I believe that's good, is it? If you
learn meditation now, a group or
meditating with a group, everyone should
remember that.
You've heard this from me many times before. It's
dangerous. When the first teacher in 1973, before
you were born, he took a pen and a tank.
Then the density of the pens would be taken. At the same time, it did
n't break, and he
said that people who
meditate together are as good as 10, just like people who
meditate alone. It's the same with
animals in a group. Nuclear power
helps,
but what's the problem in a group
situation? Someone makes the word
for noise. It's the word for
enemies, pronounced differently, but it sounds like
the same. There are
jokes about beds, and the
noises are in the
manufacturing of meditation.
If you do a group meditation, both
majors go away. That's a big
story. First, you do the
story with the pen. It's always good to
say something positive first, and
then say that little is moved by this meditation
that we are now getting from your meditation.
Because of your... You must try to
see an extraordinary amount,
while in contrast, meditation with each other.
connected
if you move halfway then
I have to the guests
a meditation will have to be blocked
try in the habit sting
like a slight little city will to sit
we in Steyr Noah and look now follows
the Aquarius 65 open every
second
we all have a mixture of good
this reason we are here in this
world we are the stupid children of the
classes who have never moved up to the next
class if you
are here out here and I am here too have
them then you have good and bad
collect now what would you not be here would
while the negative in the
seed open in a mind and important
his hair something will happen diligently
taken a fly begins that
hurts how do they go then never had
what a friend think and 31 years
not thought hurt big dolphin the
situation it is simply hard to stay
bad collect will be out of the hat
I think I have the perfect
meditation I don't have it I think
the person stationed next to the perfect wave
also no perfect
meditation but then has to fight with it
and has his move you is not
there rejoice you can if you if the
Young man, a long Harpstedt, trying
again and again to throw out
at the water, don't give up. The
three goals of ESI were played, the
big goal,
many people saw the stars yesterday, on
Monday, and the fourth star,
but the big goal is
to help billions of planets.
You will enjoy it when you are no longer
interested, first dying without knowing
what happens, not meditating very much,
then you can see these things, that
always changes you, then you will become a
fanatic, not fanatical, a
fanatic, not off the table.
If you don't do these things in your life, it's like that
everyone has done it,
only because you didn't want to, not
every day until now. That is incredibly
important, incredibly
Russian power,
I know these important things,
billions of stars
in Serbia, billions of beings to
see and read, to have
these experiences once in
your life,
and the meditation, the points now,
make
this connected with the next part of the
noise that we then make, we have
his eyes closed.
If you try after that with actions
and you have your  Keep your eyes slightly
open,
but don't look at it like that.
It's helpful to
meditate in front of something like a wall that has no pattern, so patternless, nothing at all.
If you
decide
to meditate with your eyes open, slightly open,
this is something you see, like a
wall in one color.
The nose is observed, but that doesn't mean
you're aiming for the nose.
It's not that you're actually
trying to focus on the tip of the nose. The presence of the
woman of Ios prepares the
eyes a little bit away from the nose
because focusing in empty space
is magic. Then you can experiment with
keeping your eyes slightly open,
but not... I have nothing to
concentrate on. Bark military in
meditation more try to get people to
relax their face. It
's natural, my father is a
vintner. The spirit then pulls and
begins to show this as tensing
the face and tension, especially
between the eyebrows. This is called...
that means that forces give... that
means keeping this area
free... checked the environment
between the  eyebrows and relax
the area a subscription price where he is
another place Diego all of us
get tension is in the corners of the mouth
I like to paint this picture of the slightly
Lisa smiles as annoying in pink
because they will channels down to
their asset arena attract themselves
as then the meditation will be better because
the brown flows well
child check a finger
laws violate are the hands
tense or are they relaxed there are
two ways you can hold yours
can then just let it hang out of
course also no or local unless
a little shine a little
tension against that I have and
get into this habit doctor suffers
somewhat the muscles very slightly in
your stomach to tense ministry in
meditative of the meditation then
opens the underwear on a
little corresponding mass
that relaxes the corresponding muscles
on the back of the body in
Grenchen a large area for tension
to the sky am in a human
being my experiment can standard
experiment be place hold hands
on knees is to pull back a little
great  Müller,
that's the open your shoulders,
trying to check if
your sister is more tense than
the others. All human beings
have no problems, partly the
reason why, if I'm perfectly balanced,
he's right- or left-handed. They tend to
use one hand more
than the other, and that's supposed to be twisted a little.
Therefore,
Dennis is to blame, then immediately
fits the balance sheet, tells to
reject it.
It's easier if you have your hands 23
centimeters back on the middle of your
thighs and your hands on
or above your knees. Then
cut the dance so that the shoulders come together
correctly, because quite a little bit
over the horizon.
Safina, I know, as often as you can
during yoga sessions, sinking
has an influence on how clearly
you think you're
moving. You can
experiment with it, even with your eyes
closed. Where do you put your eyes?
Klaus knew
after you closed your eyes. Although
something else is an alternative choice, Castro,
look down like the white  Klaas with his
eyes closed,
but if you mean that,
then it makes the mind darker, heavier,
which again only leads to the point where they
need it,
moved in a way that makes you a little intense,
if you are a little convinced, at some point it
went as if you are driving, you look, they
do this in the
distance, the ice as 2000, a little
above the normal level, their enemy would
feel, the greatest spa, which leads to
the positive effect then haunts
yoga meditation, even in
meditation, when your eyes
are closed, there is a very big difference, a
big breakthrough, as if you can
raise your eyes a little, you can, occasion, day,
a last will, last
acquaintance, a last check of the hand, the
face relaxed, are the hands
relaxed,
the one from out or perhaps very slightly
dressed,
Lars day, the last check for now
before you begin to meditate, potencies,
try to discover tensions, and in the eyes,
between the eyelids, eyebrows,
in the microtubules, it went, now
we go, equip, they are qualification, that
we, to move, already the bidder, Magna again
Markus Hartmann, a young Danish woman, has started observing in Juba.
Generally, it's good that you
can breathe through your nose, but if you
're stuffy or it's difficult, then it's
also okay to breathe through your mouth.
While you breathe through your nose, there's
a little trick you can always do: draw it up
higher. Of course, it
goes through the wet nose, such as
down to bindings through
your dragon. How much of this
breathing into the sinuses
differentiates makes a
difference that affects your government,
so you are able
to draw it up a little higher into your head while inhaling.
This applies to opening up the nuclear power plant so that I
get that back, just more
oxygen, more breathing.
That's tradition. Counting ten breaths
is very important to start with the
payout.
Extra young and used, and that's called
flawless
when you realize when you've successfully completed
their moment. It's important to get all the air
out
during these ten breaths.
Choose the option that we exhale all the air.
The lungs will simply
take a break. Do you know  Now, once
during a move for the long one,
the quite long after exhalation with a
shorter time after the units of the
index during the episode, rich to
meditate, Britpop tries to
exhale more than the natural way out. It
is that he, the young gentlemen, after the
end of the statements, a lead organizer
tries to expel a little more
air. I will be consciously included in
this classification, and it
happens automatically. We don't think about it,
but as if with the noblest,
meditated meditation is much better if
you learn excess air that would remain in the
lungs
during exhalation. With People magazine,
I told people similarly, don't
overthink it.
Your body can, you can imagine, this happens
automatically. You start thinking about it, always having to
think about it. To classify,
we would already be there. Now, don't think about the
unit. We are
very aware of how it
worked for us. Long in the finest, which was great, tasted great.
Then we begin to
breathe to C-Max gentlemen. You have
one, all the contents of a hand
apart. Experts, also two
students, the tradition is that you
count to ten where the uplink without
anything  to think differently when the
mental gathering happening matures
or 665 per second that open together,
the 65 together went the first so far
as bringing in the negotiation
and then the breathing,
it is probably impossible for humans, they
are now, but you eat them,
then the old thinking can
decide, the doctors want to exclude the world from
him outside and Mr.
Tanja, ten breaths, internationally speaking, it was
when you get five art at a stranger's friend
from the Ma Lin from the high school, your
money comes back in Ghostbusters part
above, then you should start again from the beginning,
that yes, honestly, you are, you
probably never go to a meditation,
so try it a few times,
at least if you are correct. Besides,
now Parnassus is there, then the
planner flows better in your body and you don't
get pneumonia.
The constitution means that the
amount of air
we carry it on is built up even more
and that the planner stays in the
heart, which is only there. Joints
get special headaches,
I have no pressure, no
headaches.
If you get these symptoms
because of the meditation in his  Content:
minor pain or excitement, heart
and breathing become
irregular, a finger begins to
tremble,
or you are excited because of the
meditation. In the text, this caste had to
solve most of these problems
correctly, to order during
meditation. This is a good
solution for this problem, which comes from
meditating for a long time.
The problem is not addressed because the
climate will not always be cheerful, conscious, from
breaths. His
face has been like this since morning,
not so often.
He says today his eyes are relaxed.
19 years and would have worked in a
combined company. Someone for this important
position. My wife has often been annoyed and tense in a
hotel. In the
company, Topps is the only one who doesn't have this. Not
so in the area. In the 800-person
building,
the count's statement brings up that you
met. Did you ask people?
Is the weather today? Can you
give him a weather report?
That's what she always meant. Is in
a bad mood or in a
good mood? In the PPC, yes, a little bit.
Heard on the radio today. That's what the rain
could be. It's a bit consistent. The USA
is a secret kind.  And wisely, all
employees are told not to go into the
office today, on the ground floor, let them
look at a weather report.
But my husband, with his own mind and heart,
praised the one outside. Once, the
whole time, I slept well. Is my
okay now? My jet lag is good. My
mentor is my mental state. As
before, the manager is wet to
begin meditating
after data,
because the nasty own mind only
spends a few minutes as the situation is more
relaxed. Today, my, have fun
watching how they
got the weather report. Did you mean
that music is good for the mind?
Although it is peaceful, Smalling meant
flowing. Michael Ballack
might think of other things too, but
that is part of the weather report. Comeback,
and then comes back that the house
means that the stylist yesterday didn't
prevent something.
We get a weather report.
The theme of the third way is too easy, and
before the sign for unity, this
week is the same. The theme
this week is communication in the ring.
Kircher, the Sanskrit word, English,
knows that I know all these  Plans, that's
not much
you can see here. He's a
leader on the via ferrata. Individual
character is defined by an exact... something like that
feels like creating and how to even
assume if you now contain the toxins.
Now that's the wound, but it
's unpleasant.
I believe it's also a clash. 1
means more done.
Negative thoughts in his money are in
thoughts in their one day. In a
guest, they will learn for a week.
End of the Finnish. The definition, but the
same, is very mobile.
September,
there I find the definition. Merkel's
revolution in Buddhism is a thought that
disturbs the peace of your mind as well as the
peace of mind of the person who
has the thought. It disturbs that. It will be very, very
proud. It's a mind and then
suddenly releases the way to
think about the team. The surface of a... the
natural surface. This game is
surfing.
I surfed a lot in the early
moment. It's in the earlier... before the
summer... makes... in the summer... Chinese... the
ocean is quite good. A lot of glass...
that hasn't been there yet...
and there isn't much energy to make it crystal clear.
Naturally, the natural
state of mind is crystal clear, very
clear to many, and the like comes, and
when a child comes into the plane, the
definition comes, that's actually being, and
restless waves, small calm ones become, that's
not good for surfing if you don't
continue too long, but in
common, we have another port
weather report, something similar, and the
glass,
normally, we make up, in the year, drive,
game day, in which we slept well,
means, it's clear, it's yesterday, let it be, it just has to be
good in terms of functionality, is of
course, great, clear level, because they
steer the things we should do during the day,
relentlessly on course, unstoppable,
finger-watching,
I think, of course, the
challenges in our lives
provide
an experiment, the multi-man this
morning, an experiment, and a success of
concentrate is on the crystal-clear, the
crystal-clear mind, the money, just as it sounds
different, undisturbed, a simple
life, then we will quite consciously bring a
wink, whirlwind, storm into it,
he's right about that, help,
I will help you destroy the peace of your
mind, okay, we started
as a mine, concentrated the mind  The
design stays inside, still water is
crystal clear, soon the guests
for peace.
The still glass is glass boxes of the mind,
only strong for a few minutes. The
stomach is still a little
tense.
The invitations still go higher
into the head. Is it a fan who
says the face, the fingers are once
relaxed, exile out as if they
always consciously.
The crystal-clear surface of the guests is
of course quite even, smooth, does
n't try to move. When we move,
then the meaning of our... well,
now maybe for the first time in
his life as Presley, you have us quite
consciously at home. Do you have a storm in the mind to
create?
Let's be quite consciously and purposefully
and crystal clear. The crystal-clear water,
we all want from ourselves alone in
our lives. I myself every week, including the indoor pool, there are
challenges that are
1000 times bad. Is a person in July in
your life?
Us girl in Jesus problems that cause
difficulties. He now that
this is a situation in yourself,
in your health, media. Now
maybe it's a partner, will this be
a problem?  a relationship hippmann
wife the people you
work with like YouTube partners
I would like that here quite well
judged as an unpleasant
place would go and the live server
areas ruined was aware that if
the meditation is goal-oriented 1 church
conviction focuses
exclusively on context something
may ask someone who remembers the problems tradition
of the case where from
year to year
the from pieper certain people make
problems
feels incredibly important a
moment and a year later you ca
n't even imagine how
bad weather is like
this week you are in this mode profit
sometime the
difficulties in a row prepare his and let's get
out of the sacristy and the why my to
let the guests bring such a wind storm
over the water
I won't let go of that if you
think about her breakfast or lunch
before it's back from mini animals don't
have the choice with which I must be
really irritated
my list of all the things that have done to annoy you to get upset
otherwise there doesn't stop that there is still
Give a few more things that the city has done to you.
Now I want to breathe this in. 2003,
long statements don't open your eyes.
Moving disciplines and
meditation up until the last moment,
then slowly open the annoying little staircase.
I press questions for you. Questions about
meditation. Does anyone have one? If someone has to take the
loan, then it will be...
I don't want a longer one. Whenever
I go to the toilet, it's... go away.
Maybe I'll go too. The mean
time would be this interim period. We'll do
questions and answers. Then he has suitcases,
and already the people who have
questions will be chosen. It's his fault if he does
n't... I have a question. Once more
per person that causes me problems,
I was good myself, and I tried to
think of someone else, but then I noticed...
I was in this
situation. What should I
concentrate on?
You are... That's great. Seeing a situation...
I could be the race tomorrow or
the heart's water failure. That you're
not in a... Quite... More
points. Meditation is to be observed. It's
toxic. Readers to be observed.
We wanted to see what's in the church
and our whole lives. What makes this...
Bite guests,
meditation yoga is a goal that was
once the  To lead something irritating is
a problem, finding everything is a problem, and
you are a very special person,
but if you yourself are in Africa, that's
okay. I want us to further explain to the guys that
they observe what, of
course, has been a part of life,
but it hasn't been
noticed yet what they are doing to us.
Thank you for making me uncomfortable.
I wanted to know if there is a better
explanation or deeper complaints on the topic,
how to be stronger on everything, something
I've worked with.
Okay, that's really a great source.
You can speak from your own
experiences and small discoveries. In
my opinion, it's more passionate,
interesting,
lost places, and friends about
your own problems. Players have blown
out their own, not
told in his class, behind a
way, more passion behind it.
I have spoken, I am Mr.
Functions, with a great
return, are hollowing out here, end
consciously, 13 inhaling. I can even say
that the yoga schools say it is
very important to be for the over-
debts, and I believe caverns of
prices, and they are quite conscious. If she
only fills it with air, then it has tried it
out.  A study says I once
played when I was absolutely sure,
but then it's fun for everyone
involved. I'm working at that moment.
I think he learned, tried.
Question refers to needle. Question refers to my question.
My question refers to the body.
I would like to teach people about chronic
pain. I have
chronic pain myself. You can, you can, you ca
n't
feel mentally comfortable if you do
n't feel comfortable in your body. Are there any
tips or suggestions on what to do so
that the legs don't
fall asleep, or adjustments for
chronic pain? The question
was about chronic pain because your
days of possible suppression in the
hips,
so to act as a teacher, chatting as an educator,
and Julia, you can answer your
question, at least superficially. Causes:
painkiller, increasingly the photo with
her is or an opium, mild,
superficial, say you don't reach
now, 19 out of empty. If I'm
not senile yet, I think he's in the
talent, it's that she would
n't have consciously known that before. I have, I have
40 years, 45 to help,
answers.  members don't start and
the superficial USA was actually
both why he is very satisfied make
cooperation more effective many
media experiences answers the
press is not yes person an answer
or professional level and of that
decision deliver to connect at the
end of the day the superficial
can one on a connection with
chronic pain every day
and these things we do here after the
mediation
my doctor said would have healthy
human body if I have
seen here is now from the that is
only to take away from any opposition
no internet really practical a
new morning I think a normal
relaxed habit was is tracking
we have a program
June is for that one of you are you
right here like
no one announced me in form
they got from Congress they
got permission as may the Toni Tree million
Kilt 23 million children maybe the
biggest thing I fought for to get
income for trying
23 names already had
the last name I don't know what will
remain or not first Greenspan
is green stretching Greenspan the ASPI
the SPG SP green first  I know green, I have it,
green is the habit of
thinking about something healthy and green every day, not yet,
because he has all these
ambitions together regarding
innovations.
I have the green pen every day,
the whole program for cold
drinks is that I ever, what is
the way here?
Some people have had surgery right
here, you don't have to turn your head upside down,
do a headstand, which is what you, yes, that's
us, strong green, and help
other people who are in pain, not just
halfway.
Choose a person, the really
strange ones, the pain didn't
remind them that we suffer so much every week,
I say then, because it wo
n't be the first time, is she
how she can rely on someone, if you
have pain, then you tell
someone three times, and not to forget
the person who spends a very long time, very, very terribly,
and
maybe their hand has to be cut off,
namely, measured by GDP,
incredibly
okay, because the person
lets the people zinco, let your
green urge not go, that the topic teaches itself,
daily training, also something, which
knowledge for servers not everyone can do,
and then the dependent sick
second.  person who has the lift ticket because those
are the strengths are the
superficial ones or pen what are the
superficial ones it works another
question
[Music]
thank you erect the second time here and
when I try to make my motivation here
then my left eye tears come
out make everything clear here
I have this should the several separate
us happily or separate sadly
or just give water
happy and sad one guitarist can
say I have seen many things in my
life because of his novel in
general there is a sink Roman
language is that a very valuable
or happy water lose
[Music]
I am at 8:15